Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Papers AIA.031.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1930-2002; 8 boxes
  - Subseries C: Negatives
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 37)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 38)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 39)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 40, Box 31, Folder 104-110)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 41)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 42)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 43, Box 31, Folder 104-110)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 44, Box 31, Folder 104-110)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 45)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 46)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 47, Box 31, Folder 104-110)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 48, Box 31, Folder 104-110)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Keegan, Kevin, undated (Box 34, Folder 50, Box 31, Folder 120)
    - McComiskey, Billy: Wedding, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 51, Box 31, Folder 130)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival, undated (Box 34, Folder 53, Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Moloney, Mick, undated (Box 34, Folder 54, Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Moloney, Mick and Liz Carroll, undated (Box 32, Folder 13, Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Moloney, Mick and Seamus Egan, Aug, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Moloney, Mick, Seamus Egan and Eileen Ivers, undated (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Moloney, Mick, Seamus Egan and Tommy Sands, undated (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell and Jimmy Keane, undated (Box 33, Folder 23, Box 32, Folder 21, Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 34, Folder 60, Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 34, Folder 61, Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 29, Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 30, Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 34, Folder 64, Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 32, Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 33, Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, AUg, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 36, Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, undated (Box 34, Folder 68, Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, undated (Box 32, Folder 38, Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Ed Reavy, undated (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - Montserrat, undated (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Mulhaire, Martin, undated (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - NEA Knoxville Documentation Project, c. 1980 (Box 34, Folder 73, Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Neary, Eleanor Kane, undated (Box 34, Folder 74)
    - Old Time Musicians, undated (Box 34, Folder 75)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 76, Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 77, Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 78, Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 79, Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 82, Box 34, Folder 80)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 83, Box 34, Folder 81)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 84, Box 34, Folder 82)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 85, Box 34, Folder 83)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 86, Box 34, Folder 84)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 87, Box 34, Folder 85)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 86)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 87)
    - Rafferty, Mike and Mary, undated (Box 34, Folder 88, Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Reavy, Ed, undated (Box 34, Folder 89, Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Saint Malachy's, Aug, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 19, Box 34, Folder 90)
    - Sessions feat. McGlynn, Carroll, Coens, undated (Box 33, Folder 22, Box 34, Folder 91, Folder 24, Folder 23)
    - Shannon, Joe and Johnny McGreevy, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 92, Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 93, Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 34, Folder 94, Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Various Artists: Coens, A. O'Brien, Reavy, Cahill, DeDanaan, G. Kelly, Rafferty, undated (Box 34, Folder 95)
    - Washington Irish Folk Festival, undated (Box 34, Folder 96)
    - Wolf Trap, undated (Box 33, Folder 49, Box 34, Folder 97)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tenn) (Box 33, Folder 50, Box 34, Folder 98)
  - Subseries D: Film, 1981
    - Did Your Mother Come From Ireland? 35mm. print, 1981 (Film 39)
- Series VII: Archived Websites, April 2014-ongoing; 2 websites in two archived websites.
  The website includes Mick Moloney's event and concert listings, yearly cultural tours in Ireland, his discography, reviews, and his writings.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of mickmoloney.com in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.